http://www.onlineconversion.com/privacy.htm

Our Privacy Statement
OnlineConversion has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.
Information Automatically Logged
We use server logs, which contain your IP address, to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The information in the server logs are used to generate reports to track our page views, page errors, and referrers. This information is used only by us.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Contact information
Some forms may ask users to give us contact information (e-mail address).
Your Name and e-mail are asked for in the Tell-a-Friend program. This information is not saved on our server and is used only for e-mailing your friend.
Your Name and e-mail address are asked for when joining the message forum. This information is optional and is described in additional detail further within this document.
We will never give or sell your e-mail address to anyone without a U.S. court order.
Web Forms
Many of the forms ask you to enter information for using the conversions. Such as how many feet to convert to meters. Some may ask for personal information, such as your birthday, to tell you how many days old you are. These forms use "Client Side Scripting" and do not send any information to us. The information entered in these forms disappears as soon as you close your web browser.
Forums
We use a community type BBS for our Message Forums.
If you post messages as a guest, your name and e-mail address is asked for. This information can be viewed by anyone. Your e-mail address is not required and we recommend not giving it, and using an alias for your name, if you do not wish this information available to the public.
If you register for the message forums, other personal information is asked for. This information is viewable by anyone. Most information is optional and we recommend not giving information you do not want available to the public. Your e-mail address is required but you can make this private in your preferences. Your name is required but you may use an alias if you wish. Any information you give in the message forums is not used by us. It is used only for the message forum. Some examples are notifying you through e-mail when you request to be notified of new postings.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. OnlineConversion is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We cannot be 100% sure that nobody can hack into our server, so OnlineConversion recommends using a free e-mail service, such as hotmail, when submitting your e-mail address to sites on the Internet.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact:
Robert Fogt
BookMark Us
It may come in handy.
Are you bored?
Try the Fun Stuff
Was this site helpful?
Link to Us | Donate
Part of the BlueSparks Network.
| Privacy Policy | License
© Copyright 1997-Present Robert Fogt.
